Albin Karlsson

A software engineer student with a business background. Changing my career has been the best decision I have ever made. That being said, I do not regret my previous experiences since that has taught me other qualities I can bring with me on my journey.

CONTACT INFORMATION

Phone number:

+4673 156 25 73

E-mail:

A.L.Karlsson@outlook.com

Address:

Prilyckegatan 103, 425 32, Hisings Kärra

SKILLS

- Java
- JavaScript
- Python
- Git

LANGUAGES

- Swedish (First language)
- English (Fluent)
- Spanish (Beginner)

OTHER MERITS

Casino Cosmopol | 2018

· Award for Best Employee

AstraZeneca | 2022

• Nomination to AstraZeneca's award for the R&D project of the year

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering

Software Engineering and Management Göteborgs Universitet | Aug 2021 - June 2024

International Foundation Programme

Business and Management
University of Reading | Sep 2014 - Dec 2015

High school Diploma

International Baccalaureate Certificate American International School of Abu Dhabi | Aug 2011 - June 2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Summer Internship

AstraZeneca | June 2022 - Aug 2022

- Fullstack development
- Python Scripts

Administration Manager

Advokatbyrån Urgell | Jan 2019 - June 2021

- Recruiting
- Finance manager
- Creating relationships with suppliers

Inspector Dealer

Casino Cosmopol | Jan 2016 - Dec 2018

- Game Supervision
- Financial transactions
- Game Controller

Suppleant Hotell- och Restaurangfacket

Casino Cosmopol | Jan 2018 - Dec 2018

- Union Representative
- LUK (Lokal ungdomskommitté) (The Local Youth Comittee)